https://www.appliedmachinery.com.au/privacy-policy

On-Line Services
Generally, the Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd Privacy Statement applies to all aspects of the Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd web site. All Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd subsidiaries and joint ventures will have their policies prominently posted on their site.
Personal Information
At Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our pledge is to safeguard any personal information that you provide us, and to make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you choose. The goal of this Privacy Statement is to notify you of our online privacy practices and to describe the choices you have about the way your information is collected and used. This statement is accessible from each page of the site, and at every point where personal information is requested. It also explains the security measures taken to protect your information, your ability to access your information and whom you can contact at Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd to answer your questions about this Privacy Statement and resolve any issues which may arise.
Personal Information about Others
If you send us information about others, we will use that information (usually an e-mail address) to do what you asked us to do (for example, to send our Newsletter). At any time any personal information in our possession will be deleted from all records kept by Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd and its subsidiaries, partners, associates and affiliates immediately upon their request.
Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information
We will only use your personal information (including your e-mail address) for the purpose for which you have provided it, e.g. to register for subscription to our regular Newsletter, or in the normal course of business communications. We will not in any circumstances disclose your personal information to third parties, unless where such disclosure is required or authorised by law.
Cookies
A ‘cookie’ is a packet of information that allows the server (the computer that houses this web site) to identify and interact more effectively with your computer. Our server (in some instances) generates a temporary cookie, which is used to keep track of the pages you have accessed while using our server. The cookie exists only for the time you are accessing the Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd web server. At the end of your interaction with Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd the cookie “crumbles”, no longer existing on your computer and cannot be used for further identification or access to your machine. This web site may also store cookies on your web browser in order to improve service for you on your subsequent visits to this web site. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences). If you disable the use of cookies on your web browser or remove or reject specific cookies from this web site or linked sites then you may not be able to gain access to all of the content and facilities in this web site. For further information on cookies and this web site please contact us.
Outside Links
This web site contain links to and from other web sites and Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices of those web sites. Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd encourages you to ascertain the privacy practices of those web sites.
E-mail
Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd may send you e-mail about your access details, or in response to your questions. Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd and our subsidiaries, partners, associates and affiliates may also send you e-mail with information that may be of interest to you, unless you indicate you do not want to receive this material. We will give you an opportunity to let us know your preference regarding the receiving of informative/instructive e-mail when you register your interest in this service, when you provide us with your personal information, or when we send you e-mail. You choose not to accept this informative/instructive e-mail. This option applies to informative/instructive e-mail only, as we may find it necessary to send you e-mail relating to your access account. All informative/instructive e-mail that you receive from Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd will tell you how to decline receiving future informative/instructive e-mail. You may change your e-mail preferences at any time. See “Keeping Your Information Accurate” below.
Protecting Your Information
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place certain physical, electronic, managerial and security procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We safeguard information according to established security standards and procedures, such as using Secure Socket Layer (SSL), and we continually assess new technology for protecting information. Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd employees are trained to understand and comply with these information principles and we communicate our privacy policy, practices and guidelines to all employees. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet. At a minimum, we encourage you to change your passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure that you are using a secure browser as you surf the Internet.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Any subscriber to the regular e-mail newsletters issued by Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd can opt to unsubscribe at any time. All electronic publications issued by Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd will have a link enabling the recipient to easily unsubscribe, or you can inform us of your instructions to send no further informative/instructional material by clicking here.
Keeping Your Information Accurate
If you are a registered user of www.appliedmachinery.com.au or of any other Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd online service and any of your personal information changes, you can advise us by clicking here. For all contact information for Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd click here. We will make every reasonable effort to make sure your requests are met. To protect your privacy, proof of identity is required.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
Applied Machinery Australia Pty Ltd reserves the right to modify this privacy statement from time to time, by posting a prominent announcement on this page or, in the event of a material change, by notifying by e-mail all customers whose personal information we have retained.
Contact Us Now
I wish to subscribe to Applied Machinery Newsletter
Applied Machinery
Sheetmetal
Engineering
Plastics
Recycling
Information
55 - 61 Nissan Drive,
Dandenong
Victoria
3175
Australia.
Ph | +61 (0) 3 9706 8066
